Guide to the Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society Records
1928-2003
1928 2003
Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society
MC 00246
The records of Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society, include administrative records, papers of prominent former members, records of various committees, files on club and chapter affiliates, records of the Society's annual meeting, information related to the publication of the Society's journal American Scientist, files concerning the Sigma Xi Center, subject files, and audiovisual materials.
Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society, was formed in 1886 at Cornell University as an honor society for science and engineering; the original founders of Sigma Xi were members of the Sibley College of Mechanical Engineering at the university. Moving beyond the Society's early intention of fostering companionship, Sigma Xi has since evolved to offer the sciences a strong, unified voice in support of scientific advancement and achievement.
442.75 linear feet
North Carolina State University Libraries, Special Collections Research Center
Use of audiovisual material may require production of listening or viewing copies.
Donated by Sigma Xi in 1997, 2000, 2004.
The Records of Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society are divided into eight major series. Series 1. Administrative Records, 1937-2002 contains the records of the Board of Directors and the Executive Committee of Sigma Xi, as well as general administrative records. This series also includes the papers of some prominent members of Sigma Xi, including John Ahearne, Peter Blair, Evan Ferguson, C. Ian Jackson, and Tom Malone, among others.Series 2. Committee Records, 1952-2003 contains the records of various committees within Sigma Xi, including the Committee on Grants in Aid of Research, the International Committee, the Committee on Lectureships, the Committee on Meetings, the Committee on Membership, the Committee on Nominations, the Committee on Qualifications, the Committee on Regions, the Committee on Science and Society, and the Committee on Science, Math and Engineering Education, in addition to many others.Series 3. Chapter Records, 1928-2002 contains organization information regarding each club and chapter affiliate of Sigma Xi. This series consists of annual reports from each affiliate and correspondence between the individual chapters and the executive office of Sigma Xi.Series 4. Annual Meetings Records, 1959-1999 contains records of the national annual convention held by Sigma Xi and attended by delegates of each chapter and club. This series contains files on planning, agendas, programs, and reports of the meeting, as well as correspondence between delegates and the national headquarters regarding the meetings.Series 5. American Scientist Publication Files, 1950-2002 contains information related to the publication of Sigma Xi's journal. These files include copies of articles submitted for publication, articles turned down for publication, letters to the editor, correspondence, business information, and other general materials regarding publication.Series 6. Subject Files, 1951-2003 contains correspondence and other material concerning events, organizations, and people associated with Sigma Xi. Materials in this series represent those items that do not directly relate to the records in any other series.Series 7. Sigma Xi Center, 1989-2003 contains correspondence and other administrative documents concerning the proposal and construction of the Society's headquarters building (The Sigma Xi Center) in Research Triangle Park, North Carolina. This series also contains the architectural drawings of the Sigma Xi Center building.Series 8. Audiovisual Materials, 1983-1998 contains sound and image recordings of various Sigma Xi activities, including meetings, presentations, and the Society's Centennial film.
Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society was formed in 1886 at Cornell University as an honor society for science and engineering. The Greek letters "sigma" and "xi" refer to the words "Spoudon xynones," which translates to "companions in zealous research," the organization's motto. The original founders of Sigma Xi were members of the Sibley College of Mechanical Engineering at Cornell. Members were optimistic that the fledgling society would move engineering beyond basic mechanical and shop training to focus on an academic grounding for the discipline. The new organization also recognized the contributions of scientists - regardless of gender - by admitting women members as early as 1888.
Moving beyond the society's early intention of fostering "companionship," Sigma Xi evolved to offer the sciences a strong, unified voice in support of scientific advancement and achievement. In 1948, Sigma Xi addressed the needs of the growing number of scientists in the industry by establishing a branch known as the Research Society of America (RESA). Though RESA had its own governing board, the two societies worked closely together, eventually uniting in 1973.
After experiencing administrative difficulties in Sigma Xi's first twenty-five years, the delegates voted to create a powerful Executive Committee in 1914. This new board provided a centralized governing body for the organization. The Society's first prominent administrator, Thomas T. Holme, was named executive secretary in 1953, a post he held for the next 28 years. Holme's efforts as secretary made an immediate impact, and led Sigma Xi toward a truly national identity, as the Society and its chapters experienced rapid growth in science beginning in the 1950s. Holme steered the organization through the tremendous changes that occurred in science in the 1960s and 1970s.
Many other prominent leaders succeeded Holme in directing Sigma Xi through the challenges science presented in the 1980s and thereafter. The Society continues to grow in popularity and numbers, boasting over 550 affiliate chapters within North America and around the world. Through the Grants-in-Aid of Research program, Sigma Xi has helped to fund student scientific research for several decades. Sigma Xi also produces a bi-monthly research journal, American Scientist, to further the spread of scientific knowledge. Today, the Society works to continue the promotion of scientific research across all disciplines, and also works to honor achievements in scientific endeavors.
Sigma Xi established its headquarters in Ithaca, New York, at Cornell University in 1886. Eventually the headquarters moved to New Haven, Connecticut, at Yale University, where it remained for the better part of the twentieth century. In 1990, the organization moved its headquarters to Research Triangle Park, in the Raleigh-Durham, North Carolina area.
The records of Sigma Xi, The Scientific Research Society date from 1928-2003 and include administrative records, papers of some prominent former members of Sigma Xi, records of various committees within Sigma Xi, files on chapter and club affiliates, records of annual meetings, information related to the publication of the Society's journal, American Scientist, files on the Sigma Xi Center located in Research Triangle Park, subject files, and audiovisual materials. Types of materials include correspondence and other paper records, photographs, architectural drawings, audio cassettes, film, video cassettes, slides, and ephemera.
Materials in the Administrative Records series reflect the operation of Sigma Xi and include meeting minutes and other materials from the Board of Directors and the Executive Committee, as well as business files representing the general operation of Sigma Xi. These files address topics such as financial matters, leadership, and membership. This series also contains the papers of several prominent past members of Sigma Xi, including John F. Ahearne, Peter D. Blair, and Evan R. Ferguson.
Committe Records document some of the committees which operate under the leadership of the Board of Directors of Sigma Xi. This series does not contain records from all of Sigma Xi's committees, and is mostly limited to a few of the more prominent committees: the Committee on Grants-In-Aid of Research and the Committees on Lectureships; Membership; Qualifications; and Science, Math, and Engineering. The material found in this series consists primarily of correspondence and information pertaining to meetings each of the committees held throughout the year.
The Chapter Records series contains information regarding individual Sigma Xi affiliates and consists primarily of correspondence and annual reports. Annual Meetings Records include files related to the planning and conducting of Sigma Xi's annual meeting and forum.
The American Scientist Publication Files series contains items related to the publication of Sigma Xi's bi-monthly journal. Contents of this series include files on authors and contributors, some manuscripts used in publication, correspondence with readers, administrative records, and general reference information concerning publication of this journal.
The Subject Files series contains topical files that do not relate to the administration of Sigma Xi, but do relate to programs and the work of its members. Topics represented include the use of animals in research; Honor in Science, a guide to ethics and values in research published by Sigma Xi; various conferences and events; and the Visualization Technologies in Environmental Curricula grant project of Sigma Xi.
The Sigma Xi Center series contains the administrative files and other contractual paperwork surrounding the proposal and construction of the Sigma Xi Center building in Research Triangle Park, North Carolina. Also included in this series are surveys of the land the building was constructed on and architectural drawings of the building.
Audiovisual Materials documenting various Sigma Xi activities exist in several formats, including 8mm film, 16mm film, VHS cassette tapes, Beta cassette tapes (various sizes), audio cassette tapes, and DVDs. Recorded material corresponds primarily to annual meetings in the 1980s and 1990s; recordings used to create the Sigma Xi Centennial film; and miscellaneous recordings, including meetings of Sigma Xi committees and recordings of speeches and presentations.
Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society; Research Triangle Park N.C.; Yale University; Ahearne John F.; Blair Peter D.; Ferguson Evan R.; Sigma Xi, the Scientific Research Society; Cornell University; Science Periodicals; Societies, etc. Science North America; Videocassettes; Research Laboratory animals; Research History United States; Research Finance; Science History United States; Science United States Congresses
- Administrative Records, 1937-2002; 1937 2002; 98.25 linear feet
  This series contains administrative records of the Sigma Xi organization, reflecting how Sigma Xi was run. Included in this series are meeting minutes and other materials from the Board of Directors and the Executive Committee, as well as business files representing the general operation of Sigma Xi. These files reflect topics such as financial matters, leadership, and membership. Finally, this series also contains the papers of several prominent past members of Sigma Xi, including John F. Ahearne, Peter D. Blair, and Evan R. Ferguson, among others.
  Materials are mostly arranged alphabetically within each subseries and then chronologically thereafter; as an exception, records of meetings are arranged chronologically, regardless of alphabetic topic.
  - Board of Directors
    - Ballot, 29 Jul. 1987 (Box 1.001, Folder 1)
    - Ballot, 5 Feb. 1988 (Box 1.001, Folder 2)
    - Ballot, 8 Jul. 1988 (Box 1.001, Folder 3)
    - Ballot, 3 Aug. 1988 (Box 1.001, Folder 4)
    - Ballot, 2 Dec. 1988 (Box 1.001, Folder 5)
    - Ballot, 28 Apr. 1989 (Box 1.001, Folder 6)
    - Ballot, 15 Jun. 1990 (Box 1.001, Folder 7)
    - Index to Meetings, 1964-1980 (Box 1.001, Folder 8)
    - Manual for Board of Directors, undated (Box 1.164, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 10 Oct. 1972 (Box 1.001, Folder 9)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 10 Oct. 1972 (Box 1.001, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 11-12 Jan. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 11-12 Jan. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 12)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 11 Jan. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 13)
    - Meeting, 6-7 Jun. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 14)
    - Meeting, 6-7 Jun. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 15)
    - Meeting, 5 & 9 Oct. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 16)
    - Meeting, 5 & 9 Oct. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 17)
    - Meeting, 5 & 9 Oct. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 18)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 9 Oct. 1973 (Box 1.001, Folder 19)
    - Meeting, 9-10 Jan. 1974 (Box 1.001, Folder 20)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 9-10 Jan. 1974 (Box 1.001, Folder 21)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 9-10 Jan. 1974 (Box 1.001, Folder 22)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 9-10 Jan. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 26 Apr. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 2)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 26 Apr. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 26 Apr. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 4)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 26 Apr. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 1 & 5 Nov. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 6)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 1 & 5 Nov. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 7)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 5 Nov. 1974 (Box 1.002, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 3 Feb. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 9)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 3 Feb. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 10)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 3 Feb. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 11)
    - Meeting, 25-26 Jun. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 12)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 22-25 Jun. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 13)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 22-25 Jun. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 14)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 31 Oct. & 4 Nov. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 15)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 4 Nov. 1975 (Box 1.002, Folder 16)
    - Meeting, 10-11 Feb. 1976 (Box 1.002, Folder 17)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 10-11 Feb. 1976 (Box 1.002, Folder 18)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 10-11 Feb. 1976 (Box 1.002, Folder 19)
    - Meeting, 22-23 Jun. 1976 (Box 1.002, Folder 20)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 22-23 Jun. 1976 (Box 1.002, Folder 21)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 22-23 Jun. 1976 (Box 1.003, Folder 1)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 22 Jun. 1976 (Box 1.003, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 5 & 9 Nov. 1976 (Box 1.003, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 9 Nov. 1976 (Box 1.003, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 5-6 Jun. 1977 (Box 1.003, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 5-6 Jun. 1977 (Box 1.003, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 28 Oct. & 1 Nov. 1977 (Box 1.003, Folder 7)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 28 Oct. & 1 Nov. 1977 (Box 1.003, Folder 8)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 1 Nov. 1977 (Box 1.003, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 22 Apr. 1978 (Box 1.003, Folder 10)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 22 Apr. 1978 (Box 1.003, Folder 11)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 22 Apr. 1978 (Box 1.003, Folder 12)
    - Meeting, 27 & 30 Oct. 1978 (Box 1.003, Folder 13)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 27 & 30 Oct. 1978 (Box 1.003, Folder 14)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 Oct. 1978 (Box 1.003, Folder 15)
    - Meeting, 5-6 May 1979 (Box 1.003, Folder 16)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 5-6 May 1978 (Box 1.003, Folder 17)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 5-6 May 1979 (Box 1.003, Folder 18)
    - Meeting, 19 & 22 Oct. 1979 (Box 1.003, Folder 19)
    - Meeting: Appendix, 19 & 22 Oct. 1979 (Box 1.003, Folder 20)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 22 Oct. 1979 (Box 1.003, Folder 21)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 3-4 May 1980 (Box 1.004, Folder 1)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 3-4 May 1980 (Box 1.004, Folder 2)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 10-13 Oct. 1980 (Box 1.004, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 10-13 Oct. 1980 (Box 1.004, Folder 4)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 13 Oct. 1980 (Box 1.004, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 May 1981 (Box 1.004, Folder 6)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 May 1981 (Box 1.004, Folder 7)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 16-19 Oct. 1981 (Box 1.004, Folder 8)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 19 Oct. 1981 (Box 1.004, Folder 9)
    - Meetings, 1982-1983 (Box 1.004, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 5-6 Feb. 1982 (Box 1.004, Folder 11)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 16-17 Apr. 1982 (Box 1.004, Folder 12)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 22-25 Oct. 1982 (Box 1.004, Folder 13)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 25 Oct. 1982 (Box 1.004, Folder 14)
    - Meetings, 1983-1984 (Box 1.004, Folder 15)
    - Meeting: Documents, 21-23 Apr. 1983 (Box 1.004, Folder 16)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 21-23 Apr. 1983 (Box 1.004, Folder 17)
    - Meeting, 22-23 Apr. 1983 (Box 1.005, Folder 1)
    - Meeting: Documents, 11 Oct. 1983 (Box 1.005, Folder 2)
    - Meeting: Minutes and Documents, 28-31 Oct. 1983 (Box 1.005, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 31 Oct. 1983 (Box 1.005, Folder 4)
    - Meetings, 1984 (Box 1.005, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Minutes and Documents, 4-5 May 1984 (Box 1.005, Folder 6)
    - Meeting: Minutes and Documents, 4-5 May 1984 (Box 1.005, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 5 May 1984 (Box 1.005, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, Oct. - Dec. 1984 (Box 1.005, Folder 9)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 19-22 Oct. 1984 (Box 1.005, Folder 10)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 19-22 Oct. 1984 (Box 1.005, Folder 11)
    - Meetings, 1985 (Box 1.005, Folder 12)
    - Meetings, 1985-1988 (Box 1.005, Folder 13)
    - Meetings, Apr. - Oct. 1985 (Box 1.005, Folder 14)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 19-20 Apr. 1985 (Box 1.006, Folder 1)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 18 & 21 Oct. 1985 (Box 1.006, Folder 2)
    - Meetings, 1986 (Box 1.006, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 11 Apr. 1986 (Box 1.006, Folder 4)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda, 17 Oct. 1986 (Box 1.006, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 24-26 Oct. 1986 (Box 1.006, Folder 6)
    - Meetings, 1987 (Box 1.006, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 9-10 Jan. 1987 (Box 1.006, Folder 8)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 9-10 Jan. 1987 (Box 1.006, Folder 9)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 9-10 Jan. 1987 (Box 1.006, Folder 10)
    - Meeting, 24-25 Apr. 1987 (Box 1.007, Folder 1)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 24-25 Apr. 1987 (Box 1.007, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 20 Jul. 1987 (Box 1.007, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 20 Jul. 1987 (Box 1.007, Folder 4)
    - Meetings, 16 & 19 Oct. 1987 (Box 1.007, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 16 Oct. 1987 (Box 1.007, Folder 6)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 27 & 30 Oct. 1987 (Box 1.007, Folder 7)
    - Meeting: Documents and Provisional Agenda, 31 Mar. 1988 (Box 1.007, Folder 8)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 14-15 Apr. 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 1)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 14-15 Apr. 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 2)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 15-16 Apr. 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 6 Oct. 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 4)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 6 Oct. 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 27 & 30 Oct. 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 6)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 27 & 30 Oct. 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 7)
    - Meetings, 1988 (Box 1.008, Folder 8)
    - Meetings, 1989 (Box 1.008, Folder 9)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 3 Apr. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 15-16 Apr. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 2)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 15-16 Apr. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 15-16 Apr. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 4)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 15-16 Apr. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 19 Jun. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 28 Jun. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 7)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 28 Jun. 1989 (Box 1.009, Folder 8)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 10 Oct. 1989 (Box 1.01, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 26-29 Oct. 1989 (Box 1.01, Folder 2)
    - Meeting: Documents, 26-29 Oct. 1989 (Box 1.01, Folder 3)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 26-29 Oct. 1989 (Box 1.01, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 6-9 Apr. 1990 (Box 1.01, Folder 5)
    - Meeting: Documents, 6-9 Apr. 1990 (Box 1.01, Folder 6)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 7-8 Apr. 1990 (Box 1.01, Folder 7)
    - Meeting: Documents, 25 & 28 Oct. 1990 (Box 1.01, Folder 8)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 25 & 28 Oct. 1990 (Box 1.01, Folder 9)
    - Meeting, 19-21 Apr. 1991 (Box 1.01, Folder 10)
    - Meeting: Minutes and Documents, 14 & 16 Nov. 1991 (Box 1.01, Folder 11)
    - Meeting: Minutes and Documents, 2-3 May 1992 (Box 1.011, Folder 1)
    - Meeting: Provisional Agenda and Documents, 2-3 May 1992 (Box 1.011, Folder 2)
    - Meeting, 13-17 Apr. 1994 (Box 1.011, Folder 3)
    - Meeting, 9-11 Dec. 1994 (Box 1.011, Folder 4)
    - Meeting, 10-11 Dec. 1994 (Box 1.011, Folder 5)
    - Meeting, 10-11 Dec. 1994 (Box 1.011, Folder 6)
    - Meeting, 1 & 5 Mar. 1995 (Box 1.011, Folder 7)
    - Meeting, 14-15 Jun. 1998 (Box 1.011, Folder 8)
    - Meeting, 14-15 Jun. 1998 (Box 1.012, Folder 1)
    - Meeting, 27-28 Jan. 2001 (Box 1.012, Folder 2)
    - Memorandum, Jan. 1991 (Box 1.012, Folder 3)
    - Notes, May 1990 (Box 1.012, Folder 4)
    - Notes, May - Jul. 1991 (Box 1.012, Folder 5)
    - Notes, Aug. - Dec. 1991 (Box 1.012, Folder 6)
    - Notes, Apr. 1992 (Box 1.012, Folder 7)
    - Notes, Jan. 1992 (Box 1.012, Folder 8)
    - Notes, Feb. - Mar. 1992 (Box 1.012, Folder 9)
    - Notes, May 1992 (Box 1.012, Folder 10)
    - Notes, 1993 (Box 1.012, Folder 11)
    - Notes, Jan. - Feb. 1994 (Box 1.012, Folder 12)
    - Notes, May - Oct. 1994 (Box 1.012, Folder 13)
    - Notes, Jan. - May 1995 (Box 1.012, Folder 14)
    - Notes, Jun. - Oct. 1995 (Box 1.012, Folder 15)
    - Notes, May 1996 (Box 1.012, Folder 16)
    - Notes, Jun. - Jul. 1996 (Box 1.012, Folder 17)
    - Notes, Dec. 1996 (Box 1.012, Folder 18)
    - Notes, May 1997 (Box 1.012, Folder 19)
    - Notes, Oct. 1997 (Box 1.012, Folder 20)
    - Notes, 1998 (Box 1.012, Folder 21)
    - Notes, 1999 (Box 1.012, Folder 22)
    - Requests, 1994 (Box 1.012, Folder 23)
    - Voting Results, 17 Jun. 1997 (Box 1.012, Folder 24)
  - Executive Committee
    - Ballot, 18 May 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 1)
    - Ballot, 29 Jun. 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 2)
    - Ballot, 5 Aug. 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 3)
    - Ballot, 19 Aug. 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 4)
    - Ballot, 19 Dec. 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 5)
    - Ballot, 9 Jan. 1989 (Box 1.013, Folder 6)
    - Ballot, 7 Mar. 1989 (Box 1.013, Folder 7)
    - Ballot, 19 Sep. 1989 (Box 1.013, Folder 8)
    - Ballot, 8 Nov. 1989 (Box 1.013, Folder 9)
    - Conference Call, 20 Sep. 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 10)
    - Conference Call, 18 Nov. 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 11)
    - Conference Call, 12 Dec. 1988 (Box 1.013, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (Box 1.013, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 1.013, Folder 14)
    - General, 1993 (Box 1.013, Folder 15)
    - Index to Meeting Minutes, 1942-1963 (Box 1.013, Folder 16)
    - Index of Meetings, 1976-1980 (Box 1.026, Folder 8)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 28 Apr. 1937 (Box 1.013, Folder 17)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 28 Dec. 1937 (Box 1.013, Folder 18)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 27 Apr. 1938 (Box 1.013, Folder 19)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 28 Dec. 1938 (Box 1.013, Folder 20)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 26 Apr. 1939 (Box 1.013, Folder 21)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 28 Dec. 1939 (Box 1.013, Folder 22)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 24 Apr. 1940 (Box 1.013, Folder 24)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 Dec. 1940 (Box 1.013, Folder 23)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 Apr. 1941 (Box 1.013, Folder 25)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 Dec. 1941 (Box 1.013, Folder 26)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 29 Apr. 1942 (Box 1.013, Folder 27)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 28-29 Dec. 1942 (Box 1.013, Folder 28)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 28 Apr. 1943 (Box 1.013, Folder 29)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 3 Dec. 1943 (Box 1.013, Folder 30)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 25-26 Apr. 1944 (Box 1.013, Folder 31)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 1 Dec. 1944 (Box 1.013, Folder 32)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 1-2 May 1945 (Box 1.013, Folder 33)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 29-30 Nov. 1945 (Box 1.013, Folder 34)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 17-18 Apr. 1946 (Box 1.013, Folder 35)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 Dec. 1946 (Box 1.013, Folder 36)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 30 Apr. 1947 (Box 1.013, Folder 37)
    - Meeting: Minutes, 29-30 Dec. 1947 (Box 1.013, Folder 38)